ALYSSA C BARNES

OBJECTIVE

Hello, and welcome to my resume!

I am a very hard worker, always on time and never call out. I have the ability to multitask extensively and see any assigned task through.

I began working in the service industry at 14 through my high school's culinary program. Over the years, I have learned many different people engagement skills.

I have worked in environments where I was bullied and also well liked. This created the ability to sensitively cater to both coworkers and customers in the most positive way possible, as well as leave my emotions at the door, keeping them professional.

My goal with any customer service job, is to be the reason people enjoy the atmosphere around me. I learn continuously how to succeed with this, as I continue to develop and grow within my career. Should you take a chance on me, it will be my consistent effort to not let you down. :)

- Attached, you will find a basic list of the skills that I have both learned and applied to my professional life.
- With that, is a timeline where each job has helped me develop those abilities.
- Furthermore: I have provided you with work related references, spanning the entirety of my working career.

Thank you for your time, and have a wonderful day!

SKILLS

- -15 years bar experience, 19 years serving, customer service, phone, training, management, computer, and sales skills
- -The ability to multitask calmly under pressure
- -Patience and consistently positive mindset/ attitude
- -Organizational expertise in a multitude of ways
- -Capable of long hours/ doubles with little or no break required
- -In sales, I have combined my customer service experience with targeted audience, to create friendships and generate revenue as a result.
- -Experience with CRM, communication, knowledge of KPI's, their importance, and much more.
- -Training, office, holding of keys, alarm and safe codes responsibly, regular and consistent inventory management, ordering and check in, proper cash handling, and people management.
- -Bartending, alcohol/ craft beer, and mixed drink knowledge
- -Catering, banquet, event, offsite, private, wedding, and cocktail experience
- -Traveling and concert bartending
- -Ample food knowledge, both FOH and BOH with a variety of styles; including allergy and gluten educated. Often balanced bar and kitchen simultaneously -Able to speak and understand some Spanish

CONTACT

Palm Bay , FL 772-563-3634 Alyssacbarnes@yahoo.com

EDUCATION

Vero Beach High School | Vero Beach , FL 2005 - 2009

VBHS Culinary Program | Vero Beach , FL 2006 - 2009

Indian River State College | Stuart, FL 2009 - 2010

REFERENCES

-Charlene Trager 772-979-1175 -Larry Zieglowsky (772) 643-6945 -Leslie Watkins (321) 216-6887 -Kelly Goddard (321) 343-1831 -Charlie Brownfield (321) 508-7038 -Kai Rodrigues (321) 216-5276 -Jessica Brown (772) 633-9578

LICENSES AND CERTIFICATIONS

Alcohol Compliant ServeSafe Certified Culinary Certified

WORK EXPERIENCE

Sales/ Fit Specialist

Harley Davidson | Palm Bay, FL 10/2024

Bartender/ Manager

Malabar Mo's | Malabar , Fl 11/2020 - 04/2024

Bartender; Head of Bar; Social Media Management; Key, Alarm and Safe Code

Holder

Bartender/ Key holder

Monkey Bar | Melbourne , FI 09/2021 - 10/2022 Bartender; Key, Alarm and Safe Code Holder

Bartender

Traveling and Concert Bartending | FL 02/2021 - Present Bartender

Server

Meg o Malleys | Melbourne , FL 06/2016 - 01/2019 Server

Server

Carrabbas | Palm Bay and Vero Beach , FL 08/2013 - 10/2016 Server

Bartender/ Server

Mulligan's Beach House | Vero Beach , FL 08/2010 - 09/2013 Server/Bartender

Sales Associate

Brookstone | Vero Beach and Jensen Beach , FL 08/2007 - 06/2010 Sales Associate

CPA Assistant

Complete Services | Vero Beach , FL 08/2005 - 05/2009 CPA assistant, office management and organization